I want to share what I've been able to do inside of Google
Flow for coming up with like high quality,
creative sort of brand imagery for
this cleaning brand that I've been working
on. I kind of found an unlock within
Flow that allowed me to sort of
make these high end kind of product
shots that are, I think, up to par
with some of the best creatives
out there that you see on like these really successful brands.
And how I've been able to do this is really quite
simple. It all started with references.
And so I kind of went and found a few examples of
some product imagery or shots that I thought
were really well done. These are
two of the examples. And what I did is I fed those
references into the agent that lives inside of Google
Flow. This is a newer feature they added an agent
before it was, I believe, all of it just kind
of one off prompting you would get an output for every
input you gave it. Now it's like you can do this back and forth with
the agent. So I attached these two references
as the sort of design direction and I asked
quite simply how would you describe these
from a lighting and composition point of view.
And then I followed that up, same prompt and
said I want to model this style of shot for X-All
of the brand. And then the agent came back
and basically said this is hard lighting.
It's like studio quality frozen shot still
type aesthetic. And then it asked what does
X-All sell? And so I, in that same thread,
I basically attached some reference images
of actual X-All products. And I said here
are the actual X-All products. You know,
go wild I said, kind of more or less. And what it did was
it started to generate these like action shots that
you see now. Like it took our toilet cleaning foam
powder and started to do some wild stuff with it. It
even tried to turn the X-All logo into
like a bubbly looking logo style abstract
thing. I was not even expecting it.
And it kept going with this, right? And it took all these real products
that we sell, got the packaging right. You know, there
were some outputs that weren't perfect, especially
as I got into these more multi product shots. Like you'll
notice it doesn't actually quite line up with what the
label itself says. So there was some QA I had to do still,
but for the most part, like, you know, these microfiber
cleaning cloths look great. A lot of the stuff is really
high end and high design, high quality. Colors
might be a little off, but for the most part, I think it does a really
great job. And a lot of these are just usable right
out of the box. A lot of them might also require edits.
And that's, of course, a part of the process. But for
iterating and getting an actual design direction, you know,
in place, it's pretty dang good.
You know, it's like the tablet dissolving inside of the bottle looks
great. So I wanted to just sort of share that and kind of showcase
what's possible with Google Flow. If you
find that, like, there's a brand that you're
trying to grow, start with the visuals
or, you know, if you're bored and just want to kind of see what it can
do, start with the visuals and start with a reference. So yeah,
just a quick little tidbit on how you can use
Flow to create really high end, high quality
product shots.